

CONTACT

8610496764

✓ drmariyajohns@gmail.com

EDUCATION

BACHELOR OF DENTAL SURGERY

JKK Natarajah dental college and hospital, kumarapalayam (2016-2022)

SKILLS

HARD SKILLS:

General dentistry

Restorative dentistry

Preventative dentistry

Root canal therapy

Digital radiography

SOFT SKILLS:

Communication

Empathetic

Teamwork

Dexterity

LICENSES

REGISTERED DENTIST
Tamil Nadu State Dental Council
2022 to Present

LANGUAGES

- English (Fluent)
- Malayalam (Fluent)
- Tamil (Fluent)
- Hindi (basics)

CERTIFICATIONS

Certificate of completing senior internship from GMKMCH, Salem Sep 2023- March 2024

MARIYA JOHNSON

GENERAL DENTIST

PROFILE

Friendly and dedicated health care professional with 2 years of clinical experience in providing comprehensive and personalized dental care. Passionate in esthetic and restorative procedures, guaranteed in providing painless management in all routine procedures. Besides i am interested in learning new technologies of modern dentistry that will enrich me professionally.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Senior Internship

Sep 2023 - March 2024

Govt. Mohan kumaramangalam medical college and hospital, Salem

- Working in the government sector as a special trainee aided me to enhance the diagnostic and communication skills and also to correlate dental issues with certain medical conditions.
- Performed various treatments including basic dental procedures, root canal therapy, surgical extractions, minor surgeries, assisted major surgeries under GA and LA, periodontal procedures, prosthodontic procedures, pedodontic procedures.

Associate Dentist

July 2022- Sep 2023

Krishna multispeciality dental clinic, Erode

- Assessed over 300+ patients for oral health conditions.
- Performed routine dental procedures, crown preparations, orthodontic procedures, assisted surgical extractions, implant surgeries, good in handling and treating pediatric patients.
- Collaborated with specialist to ensure seamless patient care and treatment planning. Maintained accurate and up-to-date patient records.

Dental Intern

March 2021- March 2022

Jkkn dental college and hospital, Kumarapalayam

- Completed 1 year internship.
- Conducted several screening and treatment camps in rural areas and schools.
- Worked in all the departments, performed basic dental procedures, minor surgeries, surgical extractions, periodontal, prosthodontic and endodontic procedures.